Guide to the Washington State Nurses Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Washington State Nurses Association records
1906-1980
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
1385
1385-009
Washington State Nurses Association
74.31 cubic feet (73 boxes)
Records of a professional nursing organization affiliated with American Nurses Association
Received from the Washington State Nurses Association in several additions between 1970 and 1983.
The Washington State Nurses Association was established in 1908 as the Washington State Graduate Nurses Association. It was organized by representative from five county nurses' organizations, and its original character was that of a professional organization. Much of its early activity involved establishing a system of registration and professional licensing for nurses. The organization changed its name for Washington State Nurses Association (WSNA) in 1940. The WSNA continues to be an organization limited to registered nurses, and has been affiliated with American Nurses' Association since it was founded. In 1948 the organization established an Economic Security Program to pursue collective bargaining; its first collective bargaining contract was with the Boeing Company in 1949. By the 1960s, the WSNA considered itself as much a labor union as a professional organization, and represented registered nurses in hospitals around the state as well as in industry. The organization continued to be active in supporting Washington State legislation defining the scope responsibilities and standards relating to nurses' work, and fought for collective bargaining rights for health care and public employees. In the 1980s the WSNA faced a challenge when nurses at Group Health Cooperative decertified the organization as their bargaining agent, formed an independent union, and soon affililated with District 1199, an independent union that later affiliated with the Service Employees International Union. A similar pattern emerged at other workplaces, and by 1990 almost half the WSNA bargaining units had been lost to other organizations by. Since the 1990s the two unions have agreed not to raid each other. The WSNA joined United American Nurses in 2000, and thus gained affiliation with the AFL-CIO. Later leaving to join the short-lived National Federation of Nursing, the WSNA stayed with that organization when it folded into the American Federation of Teachers in 2013, and continues to be affiliated with the American Nurses' Association as well.
Organizational records (1908-1972) include articles of incorporation and bylaws as well as organizational histories and transcripts of oral history interviews with early active members of the organization. Also included are membership and officer rosters for various periods and reports from staff and officers to the Board of Directors. Minutes of the Board of Directors and Executive Committee meetings (1913-1975) provide an overview of the association's activities during this period.
District correspondence, minutes and newsletter files (1921-1975) provide details on the activities of local units of the WSNA. Correspondence files include communications between the state organization and the American Nurses' Association, as well as with public agencies and other organizations. Areas of emphasis are health care policy, legislation to define the nature of nurses' work, and collective bargaining legislation.
Financial records (1918-1977) include materials related to the administration of a loan fund for nurses and a fund which provided welfare payments to nurses in times of special need.
Convention records (1908-1978) contain reports from constituent units of the Association, from officers and geographic (District) units, as well as proceedings records and minutes. Conference records (1949-1975) document educational conferences organized by the WSNA as well as conferences on health policy issues and nurses' working conditions and scope of reponsibilities.
Records of committees, commissions, sections and interest groups (1922-1980) contain minutes and working materials of groups focused on areas of organizational concern (committees and commissions) or areas of nursing practice (sections).
Economic Security Program was the name given to the collective bargaining activities of the WSNA from the late 1940s until the early 1970s. The associated records contain materials on organizing, negotiations, struggles for bargaining unit recognitions and agreements with a wide variety of employers. Also included are materials on economic issues of other sorts, such as wage controls in the 1970s and state and federal collective bargaining law.
Subject files contain material on a wide range of public policy issues affecting health care and nurses, publicity and public relations materials, and relations with related organizations. Research study records (1950s) include raw and processed data from surveys on conditions in nurse workplaces as well as reports.
Audio recordings, most of which have been transcribed, include interviews in the 1950s with nurses involved in organizing the WSNA as well as proceedings of the 1955 and 1957 conventions. These are recorded on 6 inch and 8 inch Audograph disks.
Records of activities of other organizations form separate series. They are part of the WSNA records because WSNA officers were also active in leading these organizations: Washington State Health Council and Washington State Joint Commission for the Improvement of the Care of the Patient (JCICP).
The records of the Politically United Nurses for Consumer Health (PUNCH) (1972-1974) form a subgroup of the WSNA records. This affiliated organization was a political action committee founded by the WSNA.
Records of two separate but related organizations are included here because their records were maintained by the WSNA for a period of time and remained with the organization. The records of the State of Washington Associated Nursing Students (SWANS) (1957-1970) are those of an organization of student nurses. The records of the Washington State Organization for Public Health Nursing (1936-1949), an organization allied with the WSNA, apparently went to the WSNA when it was disbanded.
Forms a part of the Labor Archives of Washington
Open to all users.
Records stored offsite; advance notice required for use.
Washington State Nurses Association$vArchives; American Nurses' Association; Washington Association of Nursing Students; Washington/Alaska Regional Medical Program; Washington State Nurses Association$vBylaws; Washington State Nurses Association.$bCareers Committee; Washington State Nurses Association.$bCommission on Nursing Practice; Washington State Nurses Association.$bCommittee on Committees; Washington State Nurses Association.$bCommon Interests and Goals Committee; Washington State Nurses Association.$bFinance; Washington State Nurses Association.$bHeadquarters Personnel Committee; Washington State Nurses Association.$bMinority Committee; Washington State Nurses Association.$bNominating Committee; Washington State Nurses Association.$bScholarship and Loan Committee; Washington State Nurses Association.$bAdvisory Council; Washington State Nurses Association.$bBoard of Directors; Washington State Nurses Association.$bEconomic and General Welfare Commission; American Nurses' Association.$bEconomic and General Welfare Board; Washington (State).$bState Employees Insurance Board; Washington (State).$bBoard of Nursing; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Washington State Journal of Nursing; Bulletin (Washington State Graduate Nurses Association); Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; Medicine and Health; Washington (State); Scrapbooks; Photographs
- WASHINGTON STATE NURSES ASSOCIATION, 1908-1980; RECORD GROUP I
  - ORGANIZATIONAL RECORDS, SERIES I
    - CONSTITUTION, BYLAWS AND HISTORICAL FILES, 1908-1972; SUBSERIES I (Box-folder 1/1-1/3, 14/1-14/6, 27, 28/1-28/21, 39/1, 69/1-69/2)
      - Constitution and Bylaws, 1912-1968 (Box-folder 1/1)
      - Incorporation records, 1940-1952 (Box-folder 1/2)
      - Bylaws, 1908-1949 (Box-folder 28/1)
      - Bylaws, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 28/2)
      - Bylaws, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 39/1)
      - Articles of incorporation and bylaws, 1954-1961 (Box-folder 69/1)
      - District bylaws, 1922-1950 (Box-folder 28/3)
      - District bylaws, 1951-1964 (Box-folder 28/4)
      - District bylaws: correspondence, 1965 (Box-folder 28/5)
      - Bylaws work file, 1955-1965 (Box-folder 28/6)
      - Bylaws revisions, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 28/7)
      - Model bylaws, 1964 (Box-folder 28/8)
      - Organization chart, 1970 (Box-folder 1/3)
      - Section officers, 1960-1972 (Box-folder 14/1)
      - Section rules, 1957-1968 (Box-folder 14/2)
      - Section history, 1958 (Box-folder 14/3)
      - Section organizational chart, 1968 (Box-folder 28/9)
      - History and functions of Head Nurse Branch, 1960 (Box-folder 28/10)
      - Rules and manuals, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 28/11)
      - Notes on historical source materials, c. 1958 (Box-folder 28/12)
      - Questionnaire regarding early nurse source materials, 1956 (Box-folder 28/13)
      - Responses on nursing history, 1954 (Box-folder 28/14)
      - Notes on Washington State Nurses Association convention proceedings, 1911-1954 (Box-folder 28/15)
      - Washington State Nurses Association history draft and chronology, c. 1957 (Box-folder 28/16)
      - Washington State Nurses Association history draft, c. 1957 (Box-folder 28/17)
      - History of Washington State Nurses Association - draft, 1958 (Box-folder 28/18)
      - Maps from publication Nursing Groups in Washington, 1908-1956, undated (Box-folder 28/19)
      - Recollections of early Washington State Nurses Association history by Miss Cassidy, c. 1957 (Box-folder 28/20)
      - Evelyn Constance Skooglun. Historical highlights of the Washington State Nurses Association, 1957 (Box-folder 28/21)
      - Evelyn H. Hall obituary, undated (Box-folder 14/4)
      - May Salina Loomis obituary, 1934 (Box-folder 69/2)
      - T. S. Lippy. Historical sketch of the Seattle General Hospital 1895 to 1925 (Box-folder 14/5)
      - Subject guide to Executive Board policy index cards, 1964 (Box-folder 14/6)
      - Executive Board policy index cards, 1952-1961 (Box-folder 27)
      - Committee appointment index cards, 1957-1964 (Box-folder 27)
    - MEMBERSHIP RECORDS, 1906-1979; SUBSERIES II (Box-folder 14/7-14/10, 28/22-28/23, 39/2, 49/1-49/3, 60/1-60/10, 69/3-69/4)
      - Directory and yearbook, 1925 (Box-folder 28/22)
      - List of officers, 1906-1951 (Box-folder 28/23)
      - Lists of officers, 1909-1968 (Box-folder 39/2)
      - Officer lists, 1925-1937 (Box-folder 69/3)
      - District rosters, 1967 (Box-folder 14/7)
      - District rosters, 1968 (Box-folder 14/8)
      - District rosters, 1969 (Box-folder 14/9)
      - District rosters, 1970 (Box-folder 14/10)
      - District rosters, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 49/1)
      - District rosters, 1972 (Box-folder 49/2)
      - District rosters, 1973 (Box-folder 49/3)
      - District rosters, 1974 (Box-folder 60/1)
      - District rosters, 1975 (Box-folder 60/2)
      - District rosters (part 1 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 60/3)
      - District rosters (part 2 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 60/4)
      - District rosters (part 1 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box-folder 60/5)
      - District rosters (part 2 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box-folder 60/6)
      - District rosters (part 3 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box-folder 60/7)
      - District rosters (part 4 of 4), 1977-1978 (Box-folder 60/8)
      - District rosters (part 1 of 2), 1979 (Box-folder 60/9)
      - District rosters (part 2 of 2), 1979 (Box-folder 60/10)
      - Membership data, 1930-1937 (Box-folder 69/4)
    - OFFICER ELECTIONS, 1952-1953; SUBSERIES III (Box-folder 14/11-14/12)
      - Candidate biographies and ballots, 1952 (Box-folder 14/11)
      - Candidate biographies and ballots, 1953 (Box-folder 14/12)
    - ORGANIZATIONAL REPORTS, 1938-1978; SUBSERIES IV (Box-folder 14/13-14/18, 28/24-28/38, 39/3-39/7, 49/4-49/11, 60/11-60/15)
      - Executive Secretary's report, c. 1938 (Box-folder 28/24)
      - Reports to annual meeting, 1941 (Box-folder 28/25)
      - Reports to annual meeting, 1942 (Box-folder 28/26)
      - Reports of annual meeting, 1943 (Box-folder 28/27)
      - Reports to annual meeting, 1944 (Box-folder 28/28)
      - Reports to annual meeting, 1945 (Box-folder 28/29)
      - Reports to annual meeting, 1946 (Box-folder 28/30)
      - Reports to annual meeting, 1947 (Box-folder 28/31)
      - Reports to convention, 1948 (Box-folder 28/32)
      - Annual report, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 28/33)
      - Annual report, 1950 (Box-folder 28/34)
      - Annual report, 1951 (Box-folder 28/35)
      - Annual report, 1952 (Box-folder 28/36)
      - Annual report, 1953 (Box-folder 28/37)
      - Annual report, 1954 (Box-folder 28/38)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 39/3)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 39/4)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1968 (Box-folder 39/5)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 49/4)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1968 (Box-folder 49/5)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1969 (Box-folder 49/6)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1970 (Box-folder 49/7)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1971 (Box-folder 49/8)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1972 (Box-folder 49/9)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1973 (Box-folder 49/10)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1974 (Box-folder 60/11)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1975 (Box-folder 60/12)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1976 (Box-folder 60/13)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1977 (Box-folder 60/14)
      - Staff reports to directors, 1978 (Box-folder 60/15)
      - Joint section annual reports, 1963 (Box-folder 39/6)
      - Joint section annual reports, 1964 (Box-folder 39/7)
      - District field visits, 1967 (Box-folder 14/13)
      - District field visits, 1968 (Box-folder 14/14)
      - District field visits, 1969 (Box-folder 14/15)
      - District field visits, 1970 (Box-folder 14/16)
      - District field reports, 1971 (Box-folder 49/11)
      - Plan 7 District reports, 1970 (Box-folder 14/17)
      - Joint section biennial reports, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 14/18)
  - MINUTES, 1913-1975; SERIES II (Box-folder 28/39-28/46, 36/1, 39/8-39/9, 49/12-49/14, 60/16-60/17, 69-5-70/28)
    - Councillors' and Executive Board minutes, 1913-1920 (Box-folder 36/1)
    - Western Division Board minutes, 1925 (Box-folder 28/39)
    - Board minutes, 1920-1923 (Box-folder 69/5)
    - Board minutes, 1924-1925 (Box-folder 69/6)
    - Board minutes, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 69/7)
    - Board minutes, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 69/8)
    - Board minutes, 1930-1931 (Box-folder 69/9)
    - Board minutes, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 69/10)
    - Board minutes, 1934 (Box-folder 69/11)
    - Board minutes, 1935 (Box-folder 69/12)
    - Board minutes, 1936 (Box-folder 69/13)
    - Board minutes, 1937 (Box-folder 69/14)
    - Board minutes, 1938 (Box-folder 69/15)
    - Board minutes, 1939 (Box-folder 69/16)
    - Board minutes, 1940 (Box-folder 69/17)
    - Board minutes, 1941 (Box-folder 69/18)
    - Board minutes, 1942 (Box-folder 69/19)
    - Board minutes, 1943 (Box-folder 69/20)
    - Board minutes, 1946 (Box-folder 69/21)
    - Board minutes, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 28/40)
    - Board minutes, 1947 (Box-folder 69/22)
    - Board minutes, 1948 (Box-folder 69/23)
    - Board minutes, 1949 (Box-folder 69/24)
    - Board minutes, 1950 (Box-folder 69/25)
    - Board minutes, 1951 (Box-folder 69/26)
    - Board minutes, 1952 (Box-folder 69/27)
    - Board minutes, 1953 (Box-folder 69/28)
    - Board minutes, 1954 (Box-folder 69/29)
    - Board minutes, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 28/41)
    - Board minutes (part 1 of 2), 1955 (Box-folder 69/30)
    - Board minutes (part 2 of 2), 1955 (Box-folder 69/31)
    - Board minutes, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 28/42)
    - Board minutes, 1956 (Box-folder 69/32)
    - Board minutes, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 28/43)
    - Board minutes (part 1 of 2), 1958 (Box-folder 69/33)
    - Board minutes (part 2 of 2), 1958 (Box-folder 69/34)
    - Board minutes, 1959 (Box-folder 28/44)
    - Board minutes (part 1 of 3), 1959 (Box-folder 69/35)
    - Board minutes (part 2 of 3), 1959 (Box-folder 69/36)
    - Board minutes (part 3 of 3), 1959 (Box-folder 69/37)
    - Board minutes, 1960 (Box-folder 28/45)
    - Board minutes (part 1 of 3), 1960 (Box-folder 69/38)
    - Board minutes (part 2 of 3), 1960 (Box-folder 69/39)
    - Board minutes (part 3 of 3), 1960 (Box-folder 69/40)
    - Board minutes, 1961 (Box-folder 28/46)
    - Board minutes (part 1 of 3), 1961 (Box-folder 70/1)
    - Board minutes (part 2 of 3), 1961 (Box-folder 70/2)
    - Board minutes (part 3 of 3), 1961 (Box-folder 70/3)
    - Board minutes (part 1 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 70/4)
    - Board minutes (part 2 of 2), 1962 (Box-folder 70/5)
    - Board minutes (part 1 of 3), 1963 (Box-folder 70/6)
    - Board minutes (part 2 of 3), 1963 (Box-folder 70/7)
    - Board minutes (part 3 of 3), 1963 (Box-folder 70/8)
    - Board minutes, 1964 (Box-folder 70/9)
    - Board minutes (part 1 of 3), 1965 (Box-folder 70/10)
    - Board minutes (part 2 of 3), 1965 (Box-folder 70/11)
    - Board minutes (part 3 of 3), 1965 (Box-folder 70/12)
    - Board minutes (part 1 of 2), 1966 (Box-folder 70/13)
    - Board minutes (part 2 of 2), 1966 (Box-folder 70/14)
    - Board minutes (part 1 of 3), 1967 (Box-folder 70/15)
    - Board minutes (part 2 of 3), 1967 (Box-folder 70/16)
    - Board minutes (part 3 of 3), 1967 (Box-folder 70/17)
    - Board minutes (part 1 of 3), 1968 (Box-folder 70/18)
    - Board minutes (part 2 of 3), 1968 (Box-folder 70/19)
    - Board minutes (part 3 of 3), 1968 (Box-folder 70/20)
    - Board minutes (part 1 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 70/21)
    - Board minutes (part 2 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 70/22)
    - Board minutes (part 3 of 3), 1969 (Box-folder 70/23)
    - Board minutes, 1970 (Box-folder 70/24)
    - Board minutes, 1971 (Box-folder 49/12)
    - Board minutes (part 1 of 2), 1971 (Box-folder 70/25)
    - Board minutes (part 2 of 2), 1971 (Box-folder 70/26)
    - Board minutes, 1972 (Box-folder 49/13)
    - Board minutes, 1974 (Box-folder 49/14)
    - Board of Directors referenda, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 60/16)
    - Board meeting notices and agendas, 1949-1960 (Box-folder 39/8)
    - Board meeting notices and agendas, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 39/9)
    - Staff meeting minutes, 1973 (Box-folder 60/17)
    - Joint executive committee meetings of the three nursing nursing organizations, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 70/27)
    - Washington League of Nursing Education minutes, 1939-1943 (Box-folder 70/28)
  - DISTRICT CORRESPONDENCE, MINUTES AND NEWSLETTERS, 1921-1975; SERIES III (Box-folder 14/19-15/18, 28/47, 38/1-38/53, 39/10-39/34, 60/18-60/56)
    - Capital City District #13, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 39/22)
    - Capital City District #13: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/19)
    - Capital City District #13: minutes and newsletters, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/20)
    - Capital City District #13: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/1)
    - Capital City District #13: minutes, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/2)
    - Capital City District #13: newsletters, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/3)
    - Capital City District #13, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/18)
    - Clarkston Valley District #25: correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 14/21)
    - Clarkston Valley District #25, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 39/31)
    - Clarkston Valley District #25: minutes, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 14/22)
    - Clarkston Valley District #25, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/19)
    - Columbia Basin District #26, 1950-1965 (Box-folder 39/32)
    - Columbia Basin District #26: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/23)
    - Columbia Basin District #26: minutes, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/24)
    - Columbia Basin District #26: newsletters, 1961 (Box-folder 14/25)
    - Columbia Basin District #26: minutes, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 38/4)
    - Columbia Basin District #26: newsletters, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/5)
    - Columbia Basin District #26, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/20)
    - Grand Coulee Sub-district correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 14/26)
    - Grays Harbor District, 1921 (Box-folder 28/47)
    - Grays Harbor District #8, 1965 (Box-folder 39/17)
    - Grays Harbor District #8: correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 14/27)
    - Grays Harbor District #8: minutes and newsletters, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/28)
    - Grays Harbor District #8: correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 38/6)
    - Grays Harbor District #8: minutes, 1970 (Box-folder 38/7)
    - Grays Harbor District #8, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/21)
    - Inland Empire District #4, 1951-1965 (Box-folder 39/13)
    - Inland Empire District #4: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/29)
    - Inland Empire District #4: minutes, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/30)
    - Inland Empire District #4: newsletters, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/31)
    - Inland Empire District #4: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/8)
    - Inland Empire District #4: minutes, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/9)
    - Inland Empire District #4: newsletters, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 38/10)
    - Inland Empire District #4: newsletters, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 38/11)
    - Inland Empire District #4: correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/22)
    - Inland Empire District #4: minutes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/23)
    - Inland Empire District #4: newsletters, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/24)
    - King County District #2, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 39/11)
    - King County District #2: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/32)
    - King County District #2: minutes, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/33)
    - King County District #2: newsletters, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/34)
    - King County District #2: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/12)
    - King County District #2: minutes, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 38/13)
    - King County District #2: newsletters, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/14)
    - King County District #2: correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/25)
    - King County District #2: minutes, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/26)
    - King County District #2: newsletters, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/27)
    - Kitsap County District #17, 1965 (Box-folder 39/26)
    - Kitsap County District #17: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/35)
    - Kitsap County District #17: minutes, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/36)
    - Kitsap County District #17: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/15)
    - Kitsap County District #17: minutes, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 38/16)
    - Kitsap County District #17: newsletters, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/17)
    - Kitsap County District #17, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/28)
    - Kittitas County District #18, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 39/27)
    - Kittitas County District #18: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/37)
    - Kittitas County District #18: minutes, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 14/38)
    - Kittitas County District #18: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/18)
    - Kittitas County District #18, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/29)
    - Lewis County District #19, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 39/28)
    - Lewis County District #19: correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/39)
    - Lewis County District #19: minutes, 1967 (Box-folder 14/40)
    - Lewis County District #19: correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 38/19)
    - Lewis County District #19, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 60/30)
    - Lower Columbia District #10, 1965 (Box-folder 39/19)
    - Lower Columbia District #10: minutes and newsletters, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 14/41)
    - Lower Columbia District #10: correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/20)
    - Lower Columbia District #10: minutes, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 38/21)